so what is the best kind of content to
create in your business that's going to
help you get clients my name is jerem m
Kowski and for the last 21 years I've
been helping coaches mentors and
trainers just like yourself scale their
businesses to make tens of millions of
dollars online and I've personally built
multiple coaching businesses over the
$10 million a year mark so I know what
it takes to be able to get results as
well as how to go from just starting
struggling to actually making things
work for you and that's what I want to
talk about here is in the content
creation game there's a lot of
information out there
but I work with hundreds of clients
every single week and I hear from them
what's working and what's not so what I
want to provide you with is exactly the
strategy that I think is going to work
it's working right now and will work for
you as well okay so when it comes to
content we have to think of it from a
perspective of content is used to build
trust with
people nobody's going to buy from you
unless they trust you okay so you have
to be able to build that trust with
people trust is like a bank a bank
account and when it hits a certain level
people are then willing to give you
their trust as far as that goes people
don't owe you their trust just simply
because you have value have a track
record or are awesome I mean quite
frankly I think that I fit all those
categories myself and yet I don't expect
anybody who meets Me Maybe This is the
first time you're seeing me to trust me
right away simply because of that and
become a client of mine though I would
love it that's awesome that's not
reality and so what we have to do is we
have to demonstrate to people that we
are
trustworthy and that when they trust us
that that it is not going to be painful
for them because here's the thing about
trust with human beings if you ever
lived on planet Earth and you trusted
somebody and they violated that trust
and it hurt you and now it's not safe
and you feel like next time I don't know
if I'm going to trust somebody again and
unfortunately that's how people feel
with most coaches and mentors and
trainers and especially if they're in
marketing or sales and and and people
don't trust people that are trying to
sell them
things and so you might have the best
program the best product the best
service that's out
there and people aren't buying from you
because they don't trust you that's
really the case is what we've seen
across the board in every single
business the coaches that I work with
every single day they got some of the
best programs on the planet I'm telling
you we attract some of the best people
when it comes to their their content
their coaching the Transformations they
deliver the track records they have and
here's what I found is that people that
actually have the biggest track record
haven't been trained in how to build
trust here's the
problem the people who we shouldn't
trust have mastered the ability to build
our trust so it's it's almost like this
like give and take type of a thing this
like inordinate
imbalance of the people who we should
trust don't appear trustworthy because
they just they've not been trained in it
maybe you're like I I don't know why
people don't trust me they should I used
to feel this way for the longest time
and then there's those that are like
they're they they probably shouldn't be
trusted I think about politicians even
for instance and yet people just give
their all to these people why is that
because there is a methodology for
tapping
into human
trust and when you can learn
this and I'm going to teach you some of
that here in this video and you can
apply that in your content you can get
people to buy from you okay so here's
two different types of content that you
want to create in your business number
one let me go find a a marker here I got
one right
here and I'm going to draw on the
Whiteboard right here number one type of
content this is what we call
open content okay so open content means
that it's out there and it's available
anybody can access it YouTube channel is
like open content um social media uh
Facebook page Instagram open content
that could be social media that could be
YouTube this could be a Blog this could
be a podcast
fast people don't have to register for
it they can click on it they can find
it and this is very low commitment trust
building as far as that goes number two
is what we call closed or gated
content and this is really the more
important one that you want to focus on
is that people have to register for it
You Ever Seen Those ads where you have
to give your name and email address to
be able to get a a a training or a PDF
or something like that that's a that's a
lead magnet offer that they're getting
your information to provide you with
something of value and what you want to
do is you actually want to put your most
valuable
content
gated behind people giving you their
information okay here's something I want
to challenge you with I see way too many
people that are out there giving away
stuff that they should be charging for
and they should be making people sign up
for and register for and they're just
putting it out there for free and then
wondering why nobody's buying from them
the truth is is that you want to do a
balance of both of these right here now
yes it's true you want to give away a
lot of your best content as far as that
goes if you watch my YouTube channel you
can tell I am no not stingy at all when
it comes to giving value away for free
but I have offers where you have to
register you have to sign up with your
email address to be able to get content
from me and that grows my email list and
that allows me to make a connection with
people and that allows me to then sell
to those people what I have to offer
here's the thing that you don't want to
do you don't want to sell to people in
your open content and this is the part
that a lot of people get wrong is that
they're trying to sell to people over
here they're trying to use this to get
people to buy Bu from them what's out
there for free
okay this is the only place that you
want to be selling to people is once
they sign up or they register for
something as far as that goes and I mean
a lot of people they're like well that
makes me feel uncomfortable I don't want
to make people feel like I'm just trying
to sell to them when they sign up for
something and then they'll be they're
not going to like it as far as that goes
can I tell you this that's in our head
and that's a thought process that we
have that again comes from we don't want
to be like these slimy sasy salespeople
that we've seen that are out there that
are they only care about money they
don't care about helping people but can
I tell you this if if you are somebody
and I believe that this is who you are
if you're watching this video if you are
somebody who truly cares about helping
people and you truly care about
delivering results to
people it is
an obligation that you owe to yourself
and your future clients to follow this
process and to do so confidently and
boldly and so here's what I encourage
people to do is to figure out what are
the top
areas of struggle and frustration and
pain points that people have not because
we're trying to attract people with
struggle okay we don't want to lead with
the struggle you want to lead with the
outcome that is the the negative
positive opposite of that so think about
it in terms of positive negative energy
okay so if we have this is a struggle
right here somebody's struggling to get
clients they can't seem to they can't
seem to make their advertisements work
the positive would be getting more
clients making their ads work creating
content that sells people are struggling
to ma to manage their business on their
own the positive is knowing exactly how
to hire a VA or do stuff like that so
you want to figure out what is the
positive that's the opposite to the
negative struggle people have you only
want to know what the struggle and
frustration is in your mind so that you
can come up with the opposite solution
as far as that goes now here's something
really really cool that you can do is
that you can use AI like chat GPT to
help you brainstorm what this is and so
check this
out if someone is struggling to manage a
team in their business or find staff at
a low cost list out 20 pain points and
struggles they have okay again we're not
going to be leading with these
struggles but look at these are all
issues right here that they might be
dealing with in a business now the
positive side is this watch this flip
all of these into
positives that have a desire based
approach and act as an expert in
marketing and sales copy in writing
these ideas okay so now the chat GPT is
going to go to work and it's going to
come up with ideas for how to be able to
do these things as far as that goes in a
business okay now watch this now convert
these into 20 unique YouTube video
titles and I like saying you YouTube
video titles because it's really trained
on those those names we might use it for
webinars we might use it for Instagram
reals we might use it for other pieces
of content but if we tell the AI to do
YouTube video titles it comes up with
what I believe to be better higher
quality ideas uh based on these positive
outcomes okay now watch
this top strategies to achieve Stellar
employee retention boosting team morale
how to attract track top client on a top
talent on a budget costeffective
training programs at work preventing
burnout the secret to balanced Workforce
okay so here's what I want to do here
now I want to I want to I want to
optimize this a little bit better what
if I help small business owners hire
vas what are the struggles they deal
with with hiring
vas okay so we're going to go in there
we're going to give the AI this is a
prompt and we're going to see what it
comes up with here's the set finding
qualified candidates quality control
consistency of work okay so we're
dialing in and we're optimizing some of
these ideas with the AI initially it
might not give you it the best okay flip
these into positive approaches and
outcomes using a effective persuasive
sales copy approach
okay and this gives you a lot of great
ideas again for whoops for uh content
discover top talent find Qualified Bas
with ease trust reliability guaranteed
seamless okay great now convert these
positive ideas into YouTube video titles
okay so this gives us ideas for what we
could create as content if this was your
Niche how to discover top talent find
Qualified vas
easily protect your business information
with vas uh effortless onboarding quick
effective training for virtual
assistance consistency and performance
accountability
assured uh let's see strategic task
delegation focus on what matters most
this is pretty cool let's do this um
generate 20 more ideas based on this
idea make them all unique brainstorm
okay so we're going to give it that idea
we're going to have it brainstorm 20
more ideas based on that one idea
mastering task delegation free up your
time for critical decisions you could
turn any of these ideas into pieces of
content now that are related to the to
the to the goal idea that you're looking
to create as far as whether it be a lead
magnet whether it be a topic for a uh a
webinar or a challenge or you have a a a
a short training you're going to deliver
or a YouTube video or it could be for
content on your social media and so no
matter what you're doing if you can show
people that you have a solution ution to
a problem they have and then you can
demonstrate that in your
content you're able to build trust with
people as far as that goes and there's a
process for how we communicate that with
people and I'm going to give you what
that process is right now so when you're
creating content let's take one of these
ideas right here delegate like a pro
prioritize and Achieve business goals
watch we're actually going to have ai
help us with this as well can you give
me the difference
between teaching a course on this topic
and
creating an
engaging
persuasive effective piece of
content that drives people to purchase a
coaching program on this topic the
differences between teaching versus
engaging content that leads to sales
okay watch the AI is literally going to
it's going to help us understand this
right here here are the key differences
when teaching a course your idea is
knowledge transfer
okay the primary goal is to educate them
on how to do this there's a structure to
it you're delivering content there's a
depth to it as far as that goes when it
comes to creating effective persuasive
content for sales the main goal is to
persuade the audience to become a client
of
you want to focus on benefits value
results that they will achieve from what
you're doing you want to capture their
attention quickly and maintain their
interest you want to tell stories as far
as this goes so it's more than just
teaching but it's actually making it
interactive with people to where it
leads to a very specific outcome as far
as that goes and that's different than
just teaching information to people and
the way that I I like to do it is this
is that whenever we create a piece of
content I might start with something
that teaches but I always wrap it up and
I lead it to how I can help people for
instance we have a coaching program
where I work with people on building
their businesses getting more clients
how to get more leads how to run ads
that work and everything involved in the
process of what it takes to get more
people buying their coaching programs
from them and people inv
into my program to do that with
them but again in this content because
it's on YouTube I'm my intention is not
to sell to you but I will mention it my
goal with this is to show you what it's
like to be a client of mine to
demonstrate what it's like to spend time
listening with me and so if you go
through my content if you check out how
I create content it's a great example to
you of what works in the coaching
business to nurture and build trust with
people where I'm giving value I'm giving
real gold nuggets of information but I
always always always lead to the fact
that hey I think you should become a
client of mine I think that you should
work with me and the people who do work
with me get the most results they make
tens of thousands of dollars in their
businesses okay and so that's what you
want to do and you want to do so
confidently you want to believe in the
thing that you're putting out there one
of the number number one things that you
want to make sure of when you are
creating engaging content that delivers
for sales is having a energy that shows
that you believe in what you're talking
about you're not doubting yourself
you're not second guessing and a few
ways to do this is you can either have
some notes in front of you but one of
them is to train your brain to get into
a state of mind that gets into a flow
State and that's what I find works the
best is that when people can get into a
flow state where they're not operating
out of too much thinking or logic
they're not second guessing themselves
but rather it goes from thought to
speech with no lag time I'm not taking
time to think about what I'm thinking
I'm literally thinking it and speaking
it at the same time this is a skill that
you can learn the more you create
content the better you'll get at this
have you ever noticed it seems like the
best people that are that are building
businesses successfully they can just
roll out of bed and create content well
the truth is is that they they are able
to and that's a skill that you can learn
to
extemporaneously
share create engagement and sell to
people okay but it comes from your place
of believing in yourself and having
confidence okay so one of the number one
things that it actually takes to create
engaging content is self-belief is
believing that people are going to want
to listen to
you and and and and and by the way you
might be like well I don't know if they
want to listen to me who cares who
doesn't just believe that whoever is
going to watch it is going to want to
listen to you because the truth is in
today's world anybody who's going to
spend 20 30 minutes with you to watch a
piece of content they do want to listen
to what you have to say they do want to
engage with you they're loving whatever
it is that you're sharing so you don't
need to overthink the fact that oh is
the right person listening am I saying
the right things am I am I doing this
the right way we got to learn to get out
of our head break up with the need for
other people's approval in our lives and
be willing to communicate boldly
confidently without needing a lot of
preparation without being worried about
people rejecting us without needing
everybody's approval now you might say
well Jeremiah in my business for me to
make money in my business I need
people's
approval of course we're not going to do
anything that's going to like make sure
that people don't approve of you as far
as that goes but it's that we don't want
our Focus to be I need people to approve
of me or else and that's why I notice
that a lot of people get with their
energy when they're trying to create
content is there in a needer needy I
need your attention I need your approval
perspective and what this does is this
repels people stronger than anything
else because people don't want to be
around somebody who has that kind of
energy that doesn't believe in the
themselves that doesn't trust themselves
that is worried about if you trust them
and here's the thing remember what I
talked about trust is one of the most
important
things here's the
problem when we are so focused on oh I
need your trust we appear the most
untrustworthy and so one of the greatest
things that you can do is to learn when
you're creating content let go of being
worried or concerned with what anybody
thinks about you just record it just
speak out just talk and
assume remember we're taught literally
there's this there's this whole idea The
Four Agreements don't make assumptions
it's like it's hilarious to me because
I'm like that that is the worst thing
that you can do when it comes to
creating content you need to assume that
the people you're talking to love and
appreciate everything that you're saying
and then it will come across great it'll
have the right energy to it and so one
of the biggest things that we want to
make sure of is that we're not just
delivering teaching content over
teaching OV explaining we're not just
delivering
information but we want it to be
engaging and we want it to be something
that people really want to listen to
they really want to spend time with
because they enjoy how it feels more
than just what you're saying as far as
that
goes have you ever watched a piece of
content where you're like wow this feels
really good maybe you watched a movie
maybe you watch watched a TV show and it
and it felt really good to you while you
were watching it that's exactly what
we're talking about and so when we can
learn how to tell stories in the right
way or we can learn how to communicate
effectively we can do that and we can
show up in a way that works 10 times
better than just trying to create a
bunch of explainer videos that are
teaching people stuff as far as that
goes one of the biggest things that I
that I noticed a lot of people make a
mistake of is that they're trying to
coach and transform people's lives with
their free content when you need to
treat your free content as sales and
marketing tools as far as that goes this
video right here is a sales and
marketing tool for me to build trust
with the people that I want to work with
as far as that goes okay and so for you
in your own business that's exactly what
you need to do you might be listening to
this right now and you might be saying
well I'm going to do better than that
I'm going to make the best content
that's the that's going to deliver so
much training so much value people are
just going to want to buy it from me
because it's so good it sounds romantic
but can I tell you this that that
romantic thinking doesn't turn into cash
flow in reality and and I used to be one
of those people that used to have that
romantic thinking that I was going to do
better than all these other marketers
that were out there that were they
weren't delivering the real
goods and then I was like wait a sec
okay it's I I delivered I ow overd
delivered so much that nobody wanted to
listen to
it because it was so overwhelming to
people what I was
sharing and they had no desire to to to
listen to any of
it and so I had to learn how to
communicate in a way that actually was
effective instead of being like okay I'm
going to do the best and I'm going to
make this incredible training that's
going to blow their minds that's what I
used to think of when I made content and
and I get a few hand claps but you can't
pay bills on thank yous and hand claps
so what you got to learn to do is you
got to learn how to lead people with
your content you got to learn how to
Captivate their interest and then lead
them to the outcome that you're looking
for there's a great book out there by
John Maxwell called everyone
communicates few
connect and it's really an awesome book
about what the most effective leaders do
how they find Common Ground how they
keep people's interests how they keep
their communication simple to create an
experience that everybody
enjoys and I'll tell you this the top
leaders in the world if you're somebody
that wants to be a coach that wants to
be a mentor that wants to be somebody
who trains people and makes money doing
so you got to see yourself as a leader
as somebody that leads crowds of people
that leads groups of people to an
outcome as far as that goes and when you
can do that when you can learn how to do
that the right way and you can learn
what are the things to say what's the
Cadence of how to say it and that's
something that I Mentor people on all
the time in my coaching program you can
be successful at closing sales one of
the biggest things that people struggle
with is that they're they're so focused
on the outcome that they want rather
than making a connection and so if you
can make it about making a connection
with somebody really getting to know
them and you're driving things
emotionally and you're taking things
from an emotional standpoint and
delivering them from where they are to
where they feel really good about the
engagement you provide value to them you
give them an overview of what you
promised then when it comes time to sell
them something you've built enough trust
that you're the right person for them to
work with and that's what actually gets
people to buy from you and that's what
the most effective people in online
marketing and sales do differently than
those
who struggle and I meet a lot of people
who are struggling all the time and they
have the best content they have the best
training and they have the best coaching
and yet nobody sees it nobody listens to
it nobody engages with it because
they're not understanding this art of
human connection and this art of
communication and often times I find
that they've judged others for not
delivering the goods as
well and that becomes one of the biggest
reasons why they they don't want to be
like those people so then they don't
show up in a way that is effective that
their desire to do better actually keeps
them in a hole where they're never
reaching anybody I find this to be the
case more often than not and I don't
want that to be
you okay and so if you can learn to
to open up your thinking
to the possibility of what if there was
a better way to communicate with people
where we connect emotionally where we
connect with how we're
communicating and you you commit
yourself to learning how to do this and
you join a program like my client growth
accelerator that will teach you exactly
the process of doing this with your
offers and with your marketing and with
your sales strategy you can be
successful and so listen I'd love to see
you inside my accelerator program I'd
love to work with you to help you not
just keep spinning your wheels around
but to actually get clients in that are
going to buy from you all right listen
subscribe to this Channel and make sure
to jump in my accelerator program I'll
see you there talk soon have a good one